let results = [
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Television",
        "question": "Which character was played by Dustin Diamond in the sitcom &#039;Saved by the Bell&#039;?",
        "correct_answer": "Screech",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Zack",
            "Mr. Belding",
            "A.C. Slater"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Television",
        "question": "In Star Trek: The Next Generation, what is the name of Data&#039;s cat?",
        "correct_answer": "Spot",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Mittens",
            "Tom",
            "Kitty"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Television",
        "question": "In the TV show &quot;Mad Men&quot;, what was Donald Draper&#039;s birthname?",
        "correct_answer": "Richard &quot;Dick&quot; Whitman",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Donald Draper",
            "John Ashbury",
            "Michael &quot;Mikey&quot; Wilhelm"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Television",
        "question": "In which British seaside town was the BBC sitcom &quot;Fawlty Towers&quot; set?",
        "correct_answer": "Torquay",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Blackpool",
            "Bournemouth",
            "Great Yarmouth"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "category": "Entertainment: Television",
        "question": "In the show &#039;Doctor Who&#039;, what is the name of the time-capsule model stolen by &#039;the Doctor&#039;?",
        "correct_answer": "TT Type 40, Mark 3 (TARDIS)",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "TT Type 1, Mark 3 (TARDIS)",
            "TT Type 40, Mark 5 (TARDIS)",
            "TT Type 1, Mark 5 (TARDIS)"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Television",
        "question": "Who sang the theme song for the TV show &#039;Rawhide&#039;?",
        "correct_answer": "Frankie Laine",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Guy Mitchell",
            " Tennessee Ernie Ford",
            "Slim Whitman"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Television",
        "question": "In the episode of SpongeBob SquarePants, &quot;Survival of the Idiots&quot;, Spongebob called Patrick which nickname?",
        "correct_answer": "Pinhead",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Starfish",
            "Larry",
            "Dirty Dan"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Television",
        "question": "What is the real name of the famous spanish humorist, El Risitas?",
        "correct_answer": "Juan Joya Borga",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Gabriel Garcia Marquez",
            "Jesus Quintero",
            "Ernesto Guevara"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Television",
        "question": "In which state of America was the Fresh Prince of Bel-Air born and raised in?",
        "correct_answer": "Pennsylvania",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Florida",
            "California",
            "New Jersey"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Television",
        "question": "What does Bart sell his soul for in The Simpsons episode &#039;Bart Sells His Soul&#039;?",
        "correct_answer": "$5",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "A Copy of Bonestorm 2",
            "$100",
            "A Giant Gobstopper"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "category": "Entertainment: Television",
        "question": "The theme for the popular science fiction series &quot;Doctor Who&quot; was composed by who?",
        "correct_answer": "Ron Grainer",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Murray Gold",
            "Delia Derbyshire",
            "Peter Howell"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Television",
        "question": "How many seasons did the TV show &quot;Donkey Kong Country&quot; last?",
        "correct_answer": "2",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "1",
            "4",
            "5"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "category": "Entertainment: Television",
        "question": "In &quot;It&#039;s Always Sunny in Philadelphia&quot; what was the name of Frank&#039;s wrestling persona?",
        "correct_answer": "The Trash Man",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Bird of War",
            "Day Man",
            "The Maniac"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Television",
        "question": "Which of the following won the first season of American Idol in 2002?",
        "correct_answer": "Kelly Clarkson",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Justin Guarini",
            "Ruben Studdard",
            "Chris Daughtry"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "category": "Entertainment: Television",
        "question": "Which former Coronation Street actress was once a hostess on the British Game Show &quot;Double Your Money&quot;?",
        "correct_answer": "Amanda Barrie",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Sue Nicholls",
            "Violet Carson",
            "Jean Alexander"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Television",
        "question": "Who was Firestorm&#039;s rival during the original run of UK Robot Wars?",
        "correct_answer": "Panic Attack",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Razer",
            "Chaos 2",
            "Hypno Disc"
        ]
    }
]

export default results